

BAGUS ILHAM SANTOSO

IT System and Operations

PROFILE

I'm looking for opportunities to develop new skills while strengthening the ones I already have. With my experience in the IT department for 5 years, I can work well on my own initiative and as part of a team. My main strength is my high analytical and initiative skills to complete a job. I try to learn something new from every experience because I believe there is always room for improvement both personally and professionally.

EDUCATION

• STMIK Bani Saleh Kota Bekasi 2019 - 2022

Teknik Komputer - D3 **IPK : 3.60 / 4.00**

• SMKN 3 Kota Bekasi 2014 - 2017

Teknik Komputer dan Jaringan (TKJ)

CERTIFICATION & TRAINING

- MTCNA (Mikrotik Certified Network Academy)
- **CCNA 1** (Cisco Certified Networking Academy)
- **NSE 1 & 2** (Network Security Expert)
- Menjadi Google Cloud Engineer (Dicoding)
- Belajar Dasar Google Cloud (Dicoding)

SKILLS

Network

- Mikrotik
- Fortigate
- Cisco

Program

- HTML & CSS
- PHP
- C/C++
- Bootstrap

Server

- Ubuntu Server
- Windows Server

Design

- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe XDesign

Office

- Word
- Excel

CONTACT

Telepon: ilhambagus477@gmail.com

Email : 0858-9443-9480

Portofolio:

https://bagusilhamsantoso.github.io/portofolio/

LinkedIn :

https://id.linkedin.com/in/bagus-ilham-santoso-128824163/en

WORKING EXPERIENCES

PT Intikom Berlian Mustika IT System & Operation

On Site PT BCA Digital | Mar 2022 - Nov 2022 Job Description :

- Create and Manage User Account and Computer Hostname in Active Directory
- Deploy and Configure Laptop & Desktop User
- Register and Manage IT Asset
- Support Connection Router Fortigate & VPN Forticlient
- Troubleshooting Software, Hardware, Network and Device Peripheral
- Daily Checklist Server & Hub Room

PT Intikom Berlian Mustika - IT Support

On Site PT BCA Tbk. | Apr 2021 - Feb 2022

- Checking product quality Laptop and CPU
- Re-Image OS with standard company
- Install and Update Antivirus Endpoint Security
- Respond to Service Request by ticketing system
- Deploy and Configure Laptop & CPUUser
- Withdrawal of Laptop & CPU Users
- Troubleshooting Software, Hardware, Network
- Register and Manage IT Asset

PT Arhapro

Staff IT | Sep 2017 - Apr 2021

- Deploy and Config Laptop & CPU User
- Troubleshooting Software, Hardware, Network and Device Peripheral
- Manage Database Microsoft Access
- Configure Router Mikrotik
- Planning and Developing Infrastructure Network
- Developing Website Company (Back End & Front End)
- Register and Manage IT Asset